let us uh
bow our heads for a word of prayer
heavenly father
again we come before you asking you
for an outpouring of your spirit
speak to us today lord
open our eyes open our hearts give us
understanding
and draw us to you lord as our prayer in
jesus name
amen and amen
good morning again church and happy
sabbath
so we are starting a
five-part series
today
entitled surviving
the shaking
surviving the shaking and today we're
going to be speaking specifically about
the subject of sign
confusion
understanding the end times sign
confusion understanding the end times
this is crucial for us to understand
beloved and you will see why as we get
into the message i'm going to open up
with second peter
chapter 1
and verse 19. second peter chapter 1 and
verse 19.
and uh you may want to take notes on
this message
for those of you that are watching
online i'm you probably cannot see the
slides uh there's a reason for that
today
but if you want my slides uh let me know
in in the chat if you're watching online
and i will get you my slides so
follow along um
second peter chapter 1 verse 19 the
bible says we also have a more
sure word of prophecy where unto you do
well that you take heed as unto a light
that shineth in a dark place until the
day dawn and the daystar arrives in your
heart so
the bible is letting us know here that
god has given us prophecy in order for
us to understand the signs to understand
what everyone the signs
right the signs of the times so are
important yes or no
yes signs are absolutely important
however i want you to notice something
here because
jesus i want you to notice what jesus
says about signs to a certain
uh to the pharisees and the people of
his day notice what he said
then said jesus unto them except you see
signs and wonders
you will not what
believe so now it kind of seems like a
contradiction right
god has given us prophecy that we might
be able to tell the
the signs but yet jesus turns around and
says hey listen
for some of you except you see signs
you will not believe
it's as though he was saying
that you are so caught up in
signs
that it can become an unhealthy
way of trying to establish your belief
now i want you to notice this carefully
okay
god says i'm giving you signs that you
may know the you may know the times and
yet we can become so sign dependent and
i want you to see what i mean here
because this happens several times in
scripture matthew 12 39 but he answered
and said unto them an evil and
adulterous generation seeketh after a
sign huh wait a minute god you gave us
signs so that we could know the end
times so that we can know the time we're
living in and yet jesus says and even an
adulteress generation seeketh after a
sign and there shall no sign be given it
but the sign of the prophet jonah so
what is there a contradiction here what
do you think yes or no
there's no contradiction
i want you to notice uh uh matthew 16
verse 1 the pharisees also with the
sadducees came and tempting
desired him that he would show them a
sign from
heaven now do you think the pharisees
wanted to believe jesus and that's why
they were asking for a sign
no they were asking for a sign because
of their
unbelief
it's almost as if no matter what jesus
did they would say
show us another sign
show us another sign in other words they
became listen carefully all they became
sign hungry
are you with me
they became sign hungry notice again
luke 11 16
and the others tempting him sought of
him a sign from heaven john 6 30 they
said therefore unto him what signs show
us thou that that we may see and believe
thee
uh what does what do this thou work
right in other words
here we're seeing a group of people who
are asking for signs continually
it's almost as if like remember jesus in
the wilderness
when the devil was saying
do this as a sign
and we know that had jesus done that
turn the bread to uh turn the stone to
bread satan would have asked for
another sign i'm still not convinced
give me another sign there is a danger
beloved
in becoming
sign
hungry
god has given us signs for us to
understand the time that we are in but
we can get to the place where we are
always
looking for signs and signs that god has
not given
that's the danger when we begin to see
signs and things god has not said as a
sign
because of our sign hungriness and yet
again notice what jesus said matthew 16
2 he answered and said unto them when it
is evening you say it will be fair
weather for the sky is red
and in the morning it will be foul
weather today for the sky is red and
glory o ye hypocrites you can discern
the face of the sky
but can you not discern the signs of the
times so once again jesus is not
speaking against signs
right he's saying i want you to know the
signs of the times but again we can get
to the place where we become sign hungry
and are now seeing signs everywhere when
god has not given us those signs
notice a question the disciples asked
as he sat on the mount of olives matthew
24 3 as he sat on the mount of olives
the disciples came unto him privately
saying tell us
when shall these things be and what
shall be the what
sign of thy coming
and of the end of the world i want you
to notice the two four questions the
disciples are asking
what is the sign
of your coming
and of the
end of the world so what is jesus about
to do
he's about to answer the question
twofold question
what is a sign of the end of the world
what is the sign of your coming watch
this notice how he begins
he begins by addressing the sign of the
end of the world
how many of you know what the sign of
the end of the world is just by show of
hands how many of you know what the sign
of the end of the world is
all right how many of you are not sure
what the sign of the end of the world is
it's okay to raise your hand how many of
you don't care about the question i'm
asking right now don't raise your hand
don't raise your hand
i'll be hurt
all right listen listen
and
yeah for those of you online you know
the signs of you think you know the sign
of the end of the world just put a one
in the chat if you're saying i know the
sign of the end of the world watch watch
this y'all
jesus answered verse 4 jesus answered
and said unto them take heed that no man
deceive you for many shall come in my
name saying i am christ and shall
deceive many all right let's keep going
and you shall hear of wars
and rumors of wars see that you be not
troubled for all these things must come
to pass but the end is not yet so let me
ask you a question
are wars and rumors of wars the sign
of the end
no they are not
jesus just said he said hey look here's
what's going to happen but i want you to
know
wars and rumors of war are not a sign of
the end
he just said it the end is not yet so
don't think
look a war is broken out this must be
the end
let's keep going for nations shall rise
against nation and kingdom against
kingdom and there shall be famines and
pestilences and earthquakes in diverse
places all these are the end of time
oh all these are the what
the beginning of sorrow so in other
words he's saying listen these things
are going to happen yes but they are not
the sign
of the end of the world
let's keep going verse 9 then shall they
deliver you up to be afflicted and you
and shall kill you and ye shall be hated
of all nations for my name sake
and then shall many be offended and
shall betray one another and shall hate
one another verse 11 and many false
prophets shall arise and shall deceive
many and because iniquity shall abound
the love of man shall wax coal so jesus
is basically explaining here
these are all the things that are going
to happen
i remember your question i'm getting to
it
but i just want you to know these are
the things that are going to happen in
between that time let me ask you uh were
people persecuted during the dark ages
did people betray one another during the
dark ages yeah all of that happened was
there have nations been warning against
nations yes all of that has happened
here's the thing y'all
let me just say this right now
many adventists
are looking for signs
of the end of the world am i right or am
i wrong everybody's looking for the sign
what is the sign
of the end of the world
and so we're looking over here we're
looking to what's happening in this
place in that place and we're trying to
fig everybody's trying to figure out
what the sign of the end of the world is
well i want you to notice what jesus
says but he that shall endure unto the
end
the same shall be saved all right
what does verse 14 say
and this gospel
of the kingdom
shall be what
preached where
in all the world
unto or all the world for a what
a witness onto how many
all nations and what
then
shall the end come
beloved
there is one
sign
alone
that tells us when the end has come
and that sign
is the gospel
being preached in all the world if
you're with me so far just give me an
amen if you're online give me a one or
eight in the chat we're with you pastor
jesus said it
he just told us don't think wars and
rumors of war are the sign of the end
don't think that that people betray one
another yes those things will happen at
the time and again but that is not the
sign of the time of the end that the
sign that the end of time rather i
should say that the end of time has come
that the end has come
is when the gospel
shall be preached in all the world
now
the second sign
remember the twofold question what is
the sign of the end of the world and we
just got the answer the gospel must be
preached in all the world and of thy
coming
watch this
in verse 15 the very next verse i want
to suggest to you
that matthew 24 verse 14 and verse 15
are the two most important verses in the
entire chapter of matthew 24.
in in the in all the descriptions jesus
is giving notice what happens in verse
when you therefore
shall see the abomination of desolation
spoken of by the prophet daniel
stand in the holy place who saw readeth
let him understand so watch this in
verse 14 he says the gospel shall be
what
preached in all the world the very next
verse he says when you and what's that
next word
no no no no no no see see that's
not c y'all where you that when you what
there now what is that therefore
therefore
why is it there
what's it doing there
what's it trying to tell us
this verse
when you therefore
it relates to the verse before it
i want you to catch this point y'all
this verse relates to the verse before
it
when you therefore
what's happened in verse before it the
gospel has been what
preaching all the world when you
therefore shall see the abomination of
desolation so now we know that the
abomination of desolation has something
to do with the gospel being what
preached in all the world now what
happens next verse 15 awkward
so from verse 15 he says you know let
them who's being judea flee you know
pray that your flight be not in the
winter etc but i want you to pick up
with verse 21
because it's going in chronological
order here 21
for then
shall be great walked
great tribulation such as was not since
the beginning of the world nor shall
ever be
and except those days be shortened there
shall no flesh be saved but for the
elect's sake those days shall be
shortened are you with me
watch this this is all happening when
the abomination of desolation stands in
the holy place it's in connection with
the abomination of desolation listen
then if any man shall say unto you lo
here is christ or there believe it not
for there shall arise false christs and
false prophets and shall show great
signs and wonders in some ways that
everywhere possible they shall do what
deceive the very elect verse 25 behold i
have told you before wherefore if they
shall say unto you behold he is in the
desert going out forth behold he's in
the secret chambers believe it not why
for as the lightning cometh out of the
east and shineth even unto the west so
shall also the what
the coming of the son of man be
and then verse 30 and then shall appear
the son of the son of man in heaven and
then shall all the tribes of the earth
mourn and they shall see the son of man
coming in the
clouds of heaven with power and great
glory watch verse 31 and he shall send
his angels with a great sound of a
trumpet and they shall gather together
his elect from the four winds and from
one heaven one end of heaven to the
other so do you see what's happening
here
abomination of desolation
warning of impostors
time of trouble
jesus comes on the clouds gathers his
elect
two questions have been answered here
when is this what is the sound of the
end of world when what
the gospel shall be what preached what
is the sign of thy coming when what
the abomination of desolation is seen
standing in the holy place beloved
listen to me there are only two signs
that seventh-day adventists must be
concerned with
that is it not five not ten
look what happened two signs
come on y'all need to see this
we're gonna do watch this okay i'm just
outlining it for you so verse 14 the
gospel is preached to all nations
verse 15 you have the abomination of
desolation being set up verse 21 you
have a great tribulation verse 27 and 30
you have the coming of the son of man
with the clouds of heaven verse 31 he
gathers the elect when you see the
prophetic progression
now let's backwards here's what we're
gonna no no no here's what we're gonna
do first
we're going to go to revelation chapter
14. how many of you are familiar with
the three angels messages yes we all
should be i want you to note something
here
remember we're going to compare
revelation 14 with matthew 24
chronologically
remember in matthew 24
14 the sign of the end of the world the
gospel being preached and what
in all nations
notice revelation 14 6. i saw another
angel flying mr heaven having the what
everlasting gospel to preach unto them
that dwell on the earth and to every
nation and kindred and tongue and people
sing with a loud voice fear god and give
glory to him for the hour of his
judgment is come and worship him that
made heavenly earth the sea and the
fountains of waters let me ask you a
question
does the first angel's message parallel
matthew 24 verse 14
yes it does
notice what happens next we then saw
that after the the gospel will be
preached in all the world then you have
this thing called the abomination
of desolation
let's notice the second angels message
and they're following another angel
saying babylon is fallen is falling that
great city because she made what
all nations drink of the wine of the
wrath for fornication now watch this
y'all
the gospel goes to where
all nations
what angel is this
so is there an order to these angels
so the first angel goes first am i
that's pretty basic yeah
and the first angel's job is to get the
gospel into where
all the world all nations and then the
second angel
now warns that babylon is doing
something
it is forcing what
all nations drink of the wine now
there's a reason for this y'all
i i i want you to pay close attention
attention to the chronology of these
events
let's keep moving i'm going to come back
to this
revelation 17 verse 5 17 5 speaking of
babylon and upon her forehead was a name
written mystery babylon the great the
mother of what
uh the mother of hollis and
abominations of the earth let me ask the
question do you think this cry of
babylon being fallen has something to do
with the abomination of desolation what
do you think absolutely it does
which would tell us that
the second angels message parallels the
abomination of desolation in matthew
chapter 24.
now watch this what's the what happened
after the abundance of desolation is set
in place jesus said there would be one
great tribulation very interesting what
is the third angel's message and the
third angel followed him saying sorry
that is so small and the third angel
followed them saying with a loud voice
if any man worship the beast and his
image and receive his mark and his
forehead or in his hand let me ask a
question
is that time gonna be a time of great
tribulation
the greatest tribulation the world has
ever seen
very interesting that matthew 24 is
paralleling what we read in in the three
angels messages
now here's what's even more amazing i
want you to watch this right
um
in verse 31
after the great tribulation in matthew
24 the bible then says that
jesus
let's go back
will come
with the clowns
very interesting
why is that so interesting because in
revelation chapter 14 and verse 14 right
after the three angels messages what do
we read and i looked and behold a white
what
cloud and upon the cloud one sat like
under the son of man having on his head
a golden crown and in his hand a sharp
sickle just raise your hand if you're
seeing this are you seeing the parallel
here
it is the same order
in fact we know in verse 31 of matthew
24 jesus comes with the clouds to do
what gather the elect very interesting
in verse revelation 14 verse 15 it says
another angel came out of the temple
crying with a loud voice to him of that
sat in the cloud thrust in thy sickle
and reap for the time has come for thee
to reap for the harvest of the earth is
ripe and he that sat on the cloud thrust
in his his sickle on earth and the earth
was wreaked are you seeing this
matthew 24 is the three angels messages
in chronological order
the chronological order is super
important y'all so notice it knows this
again
matthew 24 gospel preaching all the
world revelation 14 6-7 gospel preached
in all the world matthew 24 15
abomination of desolation revelation 14
8 babylon mother of abominations matthew
24 21 great tribulation revelation 14
9-12 a great tribulation surrounding the
mark of the beast matthew 24 verse 7 and
30 the coming of the son of man with
clouds revelation 14 verse 14 the coming
of the son of man with clouds matthew 24
verse 31 the gathering of the elect
revelation 14 verse 5 and 6 15 and 16
the gathering of the elect is this plain
is this simple
yes you watching online give me a one if
you're following what i'm saying now
we're going to flip this backwards
because i need you to see this yarn
the gathering of the elect
is the last thing to happen
my question is why are the elect
gathered
what is it that gathers the elect
just look at
what comes before it
ah yes the elector gathered because
jesus comes on the clouds
are you with me so without jesus coming
on the clouds violet can't be gathered
so the elector gathered because jesus
comes on the clouds we're moving
backward
why does jesus come on the clouds
because there is great tribulation
particularly against his people i'm
going somewhere with this y'all
all right so watch this
why is there a great tribulation
because the abomination of desolation
has been set up
i wanna throw my mic down right now and
just leave
i wanna i wanna just
watch this y'all
what is it
that
leads to the abomination of desolation
being set up what is the therefore in
matthew 24 15 talking about
the preaching of the gospel in the whole
world and here we are at seventh-day
adventists totally missing that sign and
looking for what's happening over in the
vatican
looking for what the pope did yesterday
did you see that oh no no no y'all
god is waiting on us
the
most important sign of the end times
is god's people
getting
off
of their lazy
lazies
god's people
ceasing to argue and fight with each
other
help us jesus
we are looking for all kinds of signs
and we're wrong
because the sign that kicks everything
off is when the gospel is preaching all
the world listen y'all in 2008
i preached this
chain reactions some of you may remember
that sermon
it's the same thing y'all i'm just
preaching it
in 2021.
it's the same messenger god is waiting
on us
we are the sign
let me simplify it
matthew 24 revelation 14 in matthew 24
the gospel is preached that parallels
the first angels message in matthew 24
you then have the abomination of
desolation that parallels the second
angels message and then you have the
time of trouble that parallels the third
english message so again if we reverse
this we have the mark of the beast
listen carefully all
why does the mark of the beast issue
come to fruition
not yet
why does the mark of the beast issue
come on the scene
because babylon
has fallen
why does what leads to this fall of
babylon
the gospel being preached in all the
world now listen to me all
if the gospel has not yet been preached
in all the world because god's people
for some reason
busy fighting with each other
what
are we doing
talking about oh mark of the beast is
right around the corner really
really
when god's people have not yet fulfilled
their commission to take the god how can
the mark of the beast be around the
corner listen carefully to me when the
whole world has not been made aware of
the issue
remember no one can receive the mark
until all know clearly what the issues
are
we are not evangelicals who believe that
you put something into your body that
you didn't know about and now you have
the mark of the beast
that just totally bypasses your mental
choice
whether accidentally or not an oh no or
a precursor come on y'all
let me read to you let let me show you
let me show you
uh um um i covered this already the the
word therefore it means consequently
these things being sold that's from
fairs from the dictionary it means for
that reason so why does the abomination
of desolation come on because the gospel
has been preached in all the world
listen
watch this y'all do you remember what
the abomination of desolation was in in
the early church in the days of jesus it
was the roman armies doing what
destroying jerusalem the roman armies
was the abomination of desolation in the
type
so watch this in colossians 1 verse 23 i
need you to see this beca beloved
because the early disciples had preached
the gospel in the whole then known world
paul says it colossians 1 23 if you
continue in the faith grounded and
settled and be not moved away from the
hope of the gospel which you have heard
and which was preached to who
every creature which is under heaven
wherefore i paul are made a minister but
i say romans 10 18 but i say have they
not heard yes verily the sound went into
all the earth and their words unto the
ends of the world in other words paul is
saying here that in his day the gospel
was preached to ought to the then not to
to his world
and it was not until that was done when
everybody had been warned about the
words of jesus pray that your flight be
not on sabbath when you see the
abomination
it was not until that was done
that rome that jerusalem was destroyed
in 70 a.d so i want you to just know
carefully gospel preaching all the world
and then the abomination of desolation
that's how it happened in the type
so what we expect to happen in the
anti-tide it's got to be the same thing
y'all and the reason why many of us
don't want to hear that is because the
burden is now placed upon us
that causes us to to stop looking for
this sign and this side and this side
and realize that we are the sign
the outpouring of the latter rain that
empowers god's people to go forth but in
in order for the odd point to happen
god's people need to be on the same page
and now you get why satan is so intent
on causing stupid
divisions
in the church
now you know why satan is so intent on
making sure that adventists never get on
the same page and realize that our
mission is to go save souls
because he knows that when the gospel is
preached in all the world not just any
gospel this gospel
he knows the end will come
notice it carefully it's right there in
the text and there followed another
angel saying babylon has fallen the
second angel has to come
after the first angel
the first angel must complete his task
in order for the second angel's message
to truly be effective
you don't believe me listen to what
ellen white says about the second angel
great controversy page 389 the second
angel's message of revelation 14 was
first preached in the summer of 1844 and
it then had a more direct application to
the churches of the united states where
the warning of the judgment had been
most widely proclaimed and most
generally rejected so watch this year
first
she's talking about a particular area
and that the gospel was preached in that
area and then the second angel
applied to the area in which the first
angel had done its work
are you with me
watch
so she goes on to say where the warning
of judgment had been most widely
proclaimed and most generally rejected
and where the declension in the churches
had been most rapid but the message of
the second angel did not reach its
complete fulfillment in 1844 the
churches then experienced a moral fall
in consequence of the refusal of the
light of the advent message but that
fall was not complete watch this as they
have continued to reject the special
truths for this time they have fallen
lower and lower
not yet however can it be said that
babylon is fallen because she has made
all nations drink of the wine of the
wrath of her fornication watch this
y'all she has not yet made all nations
do this the work of apostasy has not yet
reached its culmination
in other words beloved
it is not until the entire world has
been has been enlightened by the first
angel that babylon is then permitted
did y'all hear what i just said
how good is god
god doesn't want any soul deceived
so he says listen yeah these angels
gonna be flying consecutively and
continually but babylon will not be
fully fallen until
the first in other words the second
angels message will not be fully
completed until the first angel's
message is fully
completed
man you know that you know who that puts
a burden on
yeah
the burden is on us y'all
and and i believe that when we realize
that burden we're going to stop making
stupid oh look at this sign and that
sign we're going to stop doing that
foolishness which is what it is
and start paying attention to what god
has called us to do
you see beloved there's only two moves
left the gospel going into all the world
and the abomination of desolation being
set those are the two signs we're
waiting for
that's it
and one of them is in our control the
other one is not one of them is our move
the other one is satan's move
but satan is not allowed to move praise
god
satan is not allowed to make his move if
y'all what's taking so long god is
looking at you
are the promises certain god is looking
at you
where is the coming of the lord god is
looking at you
my church wake up
take the field
do the work
stop fighting with each other
stop stop making stop creating
diversions which are a waste of time
which which caused people to have to put
resources to combat and foolishness in
the church
let us be about our father's business
y'all
listen let's keep going uh so the great
first page 449 it says and it is not
until the issue is thus plainly set
before the people and they are brought
to choose between the commandments of
god and the commandments of men that
those who continue in transgression will
receive the mark of the beast do you see
this
the mark of the beast cannot satan does
not have permission to launch that
initiative until
the issue is plainly set before the
people
which means the first angels message
fear god and give glory to him
again she says not one is made to suffer
the wrath of god until
the truth has been brought home to his
mind and conscious and has been rejected
there are many who have never had an
opportunity to hear the special truths
of this time the obligation of the
fourth commandment has never been set
before them in its true light he who
reads every heart and tries every motive
will leave none who desire a knowledge
of the truth to be deceived as to the
issues of the controversy the decree is
not to be urged upon the people blindly
you know what
when i read that sentence
i hear god in heaven saying to satan
nope
you have no permission
to set up this decree until
people
are made aware of the truth versus the
error
and then he turns to his church and says
all right church
y'all are the ones responsible for
letting the people know the truth versus
the error
satan's waiting on us y'all
he's like
i'm trying to set this mark of the beast
thing up but uh now some of y'all have
an idea like whoa so you mean if i don't
do this we'll be around here longer yes
don't do that
that's not the right spirit
right we're supposed to be working
on behalf of our heavenly father
listen everyone is to have sufficient
light to make his decision intelligently
come on y'all it cannot get more simpler
than this i don't know why these slides
got so small but i want you to listen
carefully okay don't try to read it just
listen
the proclamation of the first
second and third angels messages has
been located by the word of inspiration
not a peg or penis to be removed no
human authority has any right to change
the location of these messages than to
substitute the new testament for the old
the old testament is the gospel and
figures and symbols the new testament is
the substance is the substance one is
essential as the other the old testament
presents lessons from the lips of christ
and the lessons have not lost their
force and in particular watch this the
first second the first and second
message were given in 1843 and 1844 and
we are now under the proclamation of the
third but all three messages are still
to be proclaimed
it is just as essential now as ever
before that they shall be repeated to
those who are seeking for the truth
by pen and voice we are to sound the
proclamation
showing their order
doing what everyone
showing their order and the application
of the prophecies that bring us to the
third angels message there cannot be a
third without the first and the second
it is not until the first angel
completes his mission that babylon is
now fallen
and it is not until babylon has fallen
the abomination of desolation set up
that the mark of the beast will be
issued
what business have we
when we are not being about our father's
business
what business have we looking at signs
and oh did you see what happened
yesterday this is a sign no it's not a
sign god didn't say nothing about that
god didn't sing them about that meeting
that was going to happen in secret over
there he said
go preach the gospel
and when you do this the abomination of
desolation will be set up
that's what he
said but we have become a sign
hungry people
show me a sign show me a sign here's
another sign oh did you see this sign
look at this sign
ellen white says the great outpouring of
the spirit of god which lightens the
whole earth with his glory will not come
until we have an enlightened people that
know by experience what it means to be
laborers together with god when we have
entire wholehearted consecrations of the
service of christ god will recognize the
fact by an outpouring of without measure
this will not be while the largest
portion of the church are not laborers
together with god are you all catching
this
are you counting why it is satan is so
pleased
when we have useless
controversies within our church
we act like the great controversy is in
the church
beloved the great controversy is between
god and satan and god's people must be
out there sharing the gospel but instead
we are
creating controversies in the church so
that we can feel holy about ourselves
stupid kinds of holiness
has someone
messaged me this morning your church is
just opening up
we've been open for a whole year with no
mask and know this we are holy i was
like wow
are you serious is this the definition
of holiness
if your church was open
we are creating these false narratives
of righteousness to make ourselves feel
good about ourselves beloved listen to
me we are all we
this is
god is trying to get us on the same page
he's trying to get us to open our eyes
so i want you to watch this okay in luke
10 verse what is the everlasting gospel
what is everlast what is it we're
supposed to be taking to the world watch
luke 10 verse 27 he answered saying thou
shalt love the lord thy god with all thy
heart with all thy soul and with all thy
strength and with all thy mind and thy
neighbor as thyself and he said unto him
thou has answered right this do and you
shall live what is the everlasting
gospel
love god
and love your wife
that's the message we're supposed to
take to the world
love god
and love your neighbor
but there's a problem though
because we can't take a message to the
world that is not working in our church
did y'all catch that
how are we going to go to the world
and tell the world love one another
how someone tell me how
because that's not the everlasting
gospel
remember what jesus said john 13 34 a
new commandment i give unto you that you
love one another as i have loved you
that you also love one another by this
shall all men and all nations every
people kindred tongue and people know
that you are my disciples if you have
love for one another the problem beloved
is that we cannot take we cannot fulfill
the first angel's message
just in word alone
because they're not gonna believe we're
his disciples so we're not gonna they're
not gonna believe the words
we might fool them out there
but we're not fooling them in here
how are we going to take the gospel into
the world when we can't even love one
another john 17 verse 21 you remember
jesus prayer that they all may be one as
thou father art in me and i in thee that
they also may be one in us that the
world might believe that thou has sent
me and the glory which thou gave me i
have given them that they may be one
even as we are one beloved we're not one
we're not one
so here's a question how do we love our
neighbor guess what it's given to us in
isaiah 58. you know the the chapter
about the sabbath
huh
that's interesting
it's not this fast i've chosen to loose
the bands of wickedness to undo the
heavy burdens and to let the oppressed
go free and that you break every yoke
isn't not to deal thy bread to the
hungry
and that i'll bring the poor that are
cast out to thy house when you see the
naked that thou cover him and that you
hide not yourself from your own flesh in
other words jesus is telling us the way
to rightly preach the sabbath and live
the sabbath is to actually love your
neighbor
aren't we supposed to be taking the
sabbath message to the world
beloved i need you to catch the
significance of this because god is
trying to wake us up as a people
he's trying to help us to see that our
mission is to actually go out and love
our neighbors and i'ma tell you some of
us do not have love for our neighbors
some of us in the church do not have no
i'm not isaiah 58 no
and we're looking at people and we're
looking at things and judging them
based on their philosophies
satan is putting a spirit of hate in the
hearts of many so-called christians
and what you don't understand i preached
about this last week is that that is a
spirit of babylon
that is the wine of babylon let me say
it this way
don't don't don't throw stones at me
the first angel's message
is what inoculates us
from the wine of babylon
let me say this way the first angel's
message
what listen carefully is god's vaccine
against babylon's virus
of deception
and beloved i will tell you now that
many of us are not vaccinated
let's see what the hates are there we
hate you pastor you're a jesuit yeah
yeah i know
listen y'all
many of us are not vaccinated against
the deceptions of satan
y'all better get vaccinated
better get vaccinated yes i said it and
i don't care if someone takes a and
says see pastor said everybody better
get the vaccine go ahead and do that
y'all know what i'm talking about you
better get vaccinated and you better be
out there telling other people y'all
need to get vaccinated with the gospel
because the virus of sin is gonna take a
whole bunch of people out and if you
don't have the blood of jesus in your
veins if you don't have the mind of
christ beloved you are going to be
deceived by that virus
the first angel's message beloved is our
vaccination drive our drive to get
people inoculated look come on man you
got the blood of jesus no i never had
the here take the blood
here here take the blood
take the blood
the virus of sin the virus of babylon if
i give you the symptoms fever
yeah you get hot easily
satanic fever
you get mad intolerant oh
chills
you're cold to people
do you have the symptoms of the virus of
babylon
praise god whether you have the symptoms
whether the symptoms are really bad you
can be healed from it
you can be healed from a beloved
listen
when the churches become living working
churches the holy spirit will give an
answer to their sincere request then the
truth of god's word will be regarded
with new interest and will exp
and will be explored as if it were a
revelation just from the courts above
every declaration of inspiration
concerning christ will take hold of the
inmost soul of the of those who love him
envy jealousy evil surmising will cease
somebody say amen
the bible will be regarded as a charter
from heaven its study will absorb the
mind and its truth will feast the soul
the promises of
god now repeated as if the soul had
never tasted of his love will then grow
upon the altar of the heart and fall in
burning words from the lips of the
messengers of god then will they plead
with souls with an earnestness that
cannot be repulsed then the windows of
heaven will be opened for the showers of
the latter rain the followers of christ
will be united in love
now you understand beloved why it is so
important that the church receive the
outpouring of the holy spirit so that we
can finish the work that god has called
us to do but in order to get that
outpouring we need to lay aside our our
wickedness and unite in love
all
right i need to get to a point here
so you'll have that in my slides
but i need you this is the last thing i
need to cover
what is the abomination of desolation
y'all need to see this
in luke 21 20 the bible says and when
you shall see the jerusalem compass with
armies then know that thus the
desolation is not so the abomination of
desolation in that time was jerusalem
surrounded by the roman armies
in the book of daniel 11 and verse 40
the same event is being described when
it says at the time of the end shall the
king of the south push at him and the
king of the north shall come against him
like a whirlwind
with chariots and with horsemen and with
many ships and he shall enter into the
countries and shall overflow and pass
over so what i need you to understand is
that this entity called the king of the
north at the time
of the end
listen carefully
king of the south pushes against the
king of the north at the time of the end
and then the king of the north
eventually comes against the king of the
south like a whirlwind chariots horsemen
and many ships and i need you to
understand something here because this
this
verse that speaks about this king of the
north coming
like a whirlwind
parallels isaiah 66 15. watch this
for behold the who
the lord will come with what
fire and with his what
chariots like a what whirlwind to render
his anger with fury and his rebuke with
flames of fire this king of the north
whoever he is is imitating the second
coming of jesus does that remind you of
matthew 24
jesus said the gospel shall be preached
in all the world and then
you're going to see the abomination of
desolation
daniel 11 is telling us that this
abomination of desolation the king of
the north is imitating the second coming
of jesus
by the way
chariots and horsemen represents land
power
the whirlwind represents air power
ships represent sea power
there is a beast from the sea
a beast from the earth
and the power of the print the power the
prince of the power of the air
the threefold union yaw is
apostate protestantism
the papacy and
satan himself
when he appears as jesus
listen to what it said by the decree of
enforcing the institution of the papacy
in violation of the law of god our
nation will disconnect herself fully
from righteousness when protestantism
shall stretch her hand across the gulf
to grasp the hand of the roman power
when she shall reach over the abyss to
clasp hands with what
spiritualism when under the influence of
its threefold union our country shall
repudiate every principle of his
constitution as a protestant and
republican government and shall make
provision for the propagation of papal
falsehoods and delusions then we may
know the time has come for the marvelous
working of satan and that the end is
near what kind of a union is it y'all
threefold it's not just the papacy it's
not just apostate protestantism but it
is spiritualism which is headed up by
satan himself
let me make it even plainer
revelation 13 13 he doeth great wonder
so that he caused fire to come down from
heaven on the earth in the sight of men
remember how jesus comes he comes with
what
with fire
this power is going to imitate the
coming of jesus and watch this it is the
miracle working power
that leads people to create an image to
the beast and all who will not bow down
will work will be killed now please
listen carefully y'all
this hasn't happened yet
and it will not happen until
come on y'all until
[Music]
listen to this
the apostle john
i'm almost done okay i promise you
the apostle john envisioned heard a loud
voice in heaven exclaiming woe to the
inhabiters of the earth and of the sea
for the devil is come down unto you
having great wrath because he knows he
has but a short time there is a time
beloved that the devil is literally
coming to us
pretending to be jesus
because he knows his time is what
and why does he know his time is short
because
the gospel has been preached in all the
world
there's no way for us to know when the
gospel free we just got to preach it
and done he will know satan will know
and god will know our job is to not know
hasn't been done yet our job is to do it
watch
fearful of the scenes which call forth
this exclamation from the heavenly voice
the wrath of satan increases as time
grows short and his work of deceit and
destruction reach its culmination
in the time of trouble now this is from
spirit of prophecy volume 4 page 440
page 440 paragraph three i want you to
note i'm reading straight here look at
what happens in the next paragraph
as the crowning act in the great drama
of deception satan himself will attempt
to do what
person a christ the church has long
professed to look to the savior's advent
as the consummation of her hopes now the
great deceiver will make it appear that
christ has come in different parts of
the earth satan will manifest himself
among men as a majestic being of
dazzling brightness resembling the
description of the son of god given by
john in the revelation the glory that
surrounds him is unsurpassed by anything
that mortal eyes have yet behold beheld
the shout of triumph rings out in the
air christ has come christ has come the
people prostrate themselves in adoration
before him while he lifts up his hands
and pronounces a blessing upon them as
christ blessed his disciples when he was
personally upon the earth his voice is
soft and subdued yet full of melody in
gentle compassionate tones he presents
some of the same gracious heavenly
truths which the savior uttered he heals
the diseases of the people and then
watch this y'all
and then
in his assumed character of christ
he claims to have changed the sabbath to
sunday and commands
let me ask you a question when does this
command to keep sunday holy when does it
happen
does it happen tomorrow
does it happen next week
no when does it happen y'all
after after the gossiping preached
after the abomination of desolation has
been set up
it is that it is satan himself
who convinces atheists
muslims
hindus
agnostics the whole world
is deceived by this miracle
if you can't get the world to agree on a
vaccine right now
what makes you think that something the
pope says or something some evangelical
says or a global warming or whatever is
going to cause people to come together
and say yeah we need to keep sunday
no y'all that's not happening that only
happens when this happens
let me keep reading
he declares that those who persist in
keeping holy the seventh day are
blaspheming his name by refusing to
listen to his angels sent to them with
light and truth this is the strong
almost over mastering delusion like the
samaritans who were deceived by simon
magnus the multitudes from the least to
the greatest give heed to these what
give he to these vaccines
come on guys come on
let us be mature seventh-day adventists
give heed to these drugs
give heed to these mental deceptions
y'all
saying this is the great power of god
watch this same reading
spirit of prophecy volume 4 page 444
same page watch satan will continue to
act a double part appearing to be the
dispenser of great blessings and divine
truths he will by his lying wonders hold
the world under his control and at the
same time he will indulge his malignity
by causing distress and destruction and
will accuse god's people as the cause of
the fearful convulsions of the nature of
nature and the strife and bloodshed
among men which are desolating the earth
thus will he
excite the great intensity the to
greater intensity the spirit of hatred
and persecution against them do y'all
see the order here gospel preached in
all the world abominations of desolation
set up
mark of the beast
it's not the other way around y'all
in the same page in the last conflict
the sabbath will be the special point of
controversy throughout all christendom
secular rulers and religious leaders
will unite to enforce the observance of
sunday and as milder measures fail the
most oppressive laws will be enacted all
of this is happening under satan
appearing as jesus christ
it will be urged that the few who stand
in opposition to to an institution of
the church in law of the church and a
law of the land ought not be tolerated
and a decree will finally be issued
denouncing them as deserving of the
severest punishment and giving the
people liberty after a certain time to
put them to death and notice the next
page the next paragraph the people of
god
will what
flee from the cities and villages and
associate together in companies dwelling
in the most desolate and solitary do you
all see this
she just described to us matthew 24.
not global warming not vaccinations not
global elites
nothing the papacy does
nothing apostate protestantism does
these things are are leading somewhere
but it is ultimately satan himself
beloved and that will not happen until
god's people
remember the problem of the ten virgins
five are wise five were foolish
the five their light went out they lost
their understanding of prophecy
let me say it again they lost their
understanding of prophecy they may have
been sign hunters
just looking for all kinds of signs and
had just disoriented them they became
prophetically crazy
and that's what we're seeing beloved
people are becoming prophetically crazy
looking for signs instead of doing what
god has called us to do y'all
the five foolish virgins they will run
to and fro seeking the word of the lord
and shall not find it because it is too
late
this is my last slide
character is revealed by a what
crisis
when the earnest voice proclaimed at
midnight behold the bridegroom cometh go
you out to meet him the sleeping virgins
roused from their slumber and it was
seen who had made preparation for the
event listen carefully both parties were
taking what
unawares
why midnight is the darkest night of the
hour midnight is when something happens
that no one was expecting and let me
tell you something beloved there is no
sign
that tells us satan is about to appear
this is why all the virgins were caught
off guard were caught unaware
we are so busy looking for signs to try
to help us to prepare when god is saying
no be ready now
be ready despite what you see going on
be ready now because you don't know when
midnight is going to hit
and how do i be ready now go preach the
gospel
some sudden or both parties were taken
unawares but one was prepared for the
for the emergency and the other was
found without preparation character is
revealed by circumstances beloved listen
to me we're in the time of the foot men
right now and and this
crisis we're facing
has revealed a lot of characters
listen
god is trying to wake us up
god is trying to source if y'all are
losing your minds
in the time of the foot men
how are you going to do
when the real thing hits because this is
not the real thing y'all
we might feel good about ourselves this
is not the thing
when nothing hits it catches everybody
unaware
emergencies bring out the true metal of
character some sudden unlooked for
calamity bereavement or crisis some
unexpected sickness or anguish something
that brings the soul face to face with
death will bring out the true inwardness
of the character it will be made
manifest whether or not there is any
real faith in the promise of the word of
god it will be made manifest whether or
not the soul is sustained by grace
whether there is oil in the vessels with
the lamb beloved how many of you want to
be ready for that time
you know who's going to be ready for
that time
those who are doing the work of god
those who are participating in the
fulfillment of the first angels message
and beloved i'm appealing to you i'm
appealing to the church i'm appealing to
you watching right now we must
lay aside
the things that divide us and stop
trying
to set ourselves apart as better than
our brother or sister
let us be about our father's business
let us be about the work he's called us
to do the three angels messages must be
fulfilled in order and if the first
angel's message is not fulfilled the
second cannot be fulfilled and the third
cannot be fulfilled but listen ya it
will be fulfilled
if god has to empty his church if god
has to shake it which he will
it will be fulfilled the only question
is will you be a part of it or will you
be one of those who think in yourself
better than others who think in yourself
holier than others will you be one of
those who will be shaken out so that
god's church can go forward triumphant
and completing this message
i want you to stand to your feet if
you're saying lord
i want to be one
i want to be among those
who help to complete the first angels
message
beloved we got to do it in a lifetime
you ever thought about that we have to
accomplish this in a lifetime that means
everybody on the planet so we better
start thinking of how
how we do this
how do we do this
we need to put our minds together and
say how are we going to get this gospel
out there like never before what how can
we use technology what can we do how can
we come together and pray together to
accomplish this mission in one
generation it can't be fight it's got to
be one generation because everybody
living at the same time must know the
truth at the same time i need to make
the decision for it or against it how we
gonna do that
let's start talking about stuff like
that
let's start talking about how we're
gonna get this message completed
instead of fighting against one another
heavenly father
you've spoken to us
you have shown us the order of events to
take place
please lord
help us to no longer be sign hunters
but help us to look at the signs that
you gave us and there's only two left
one is the preaching of the gospel in
all the world and the second one that
comes after that is the abomination of
desolation being set up those are the
two signs lord and one is out of our
control the other one is totally in our
control
the burden is upon us
teach us to be like the disciples on the
day of pentecost who came together and
prayed for the outpouring of the spirit
so that they could preach the gospel in
the whole then known world
let us be about our father's business
forgive us
for our childishness forgive us for our
foolishness forgive us for our
lukewarmness forgive us for our false
courage and our false bravado forgive us
lord
of our critical spirits
our judgmental spirits
and help us
to fulfill the three angels messages
help us
to survive
the shaking in jesus name we pray
amen
and amen
you may be seated
[Music]
either on the left side or the right
side we have tied baskets if you want to
put your ties